<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Dou Hong</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Dou Hong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PRIMARY RESEARCH EXPERIENCE</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Neural Mechanisms Underlying Compulsive Rumination and the Implications for Treatments of Mood Disorders, Changsha, China Jun. 2022-present,Supervised by Prof. Yan Zhang (Central South University)
 Conducted interviews with and tracked recovery trajectories of depressive and anxious adolescents, designed the research question to evaluate the role of rumination in the development of mood disorders based on clinical observations. Writing a review paper to summarize existing clinical and neural evidence related to the mechanism of rumination, providing assumptions about the potential neural pathway underlying compulsive rumination (which involves the ventral stratum/nucleus accumbens impairment) and discussing the implications of treatments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WORK EXPERIENCE &amp; Training (SELECTED)</title>
      <link>/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/</guid>
      <description>The Third Xiangya Hospital of Central South University, Changsha, China Student Internship, Department of Psychiatry and Neuroscience (Nov. 2017-present)
 Received training in using FMRI and conducting statistical analysis on FMRI data using MATLAB, Eprime and SPM. Facilitated therapy sessions (including CBT and mindfulness therapies) for patients with Major Depressive Disorders and Generalized Anxiety Disorders.  Oxford Machine Learning Summer School 2022, Online Jul. 2022-Aug.2022
 Learning foundations and applications of machine learning for the medical science track by attending modules, lectures, tutorials and group discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
